A Guide to the Rockefeller Archive Center records, Brochures, Pamphlets, and Clippings FA1498
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Archive Center records, Brochures, Pamphlets, and Clippings
1973-1995
Rockefeller Archive Center
FA1498
0.19 Cubic Feet One half-letter document box.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research.
Arrangement
Alphabetical.
Scope and Contents
Includes brochures and pamphlets of the Rockefeller Archive Center its activities and programs. Also includes clippings, past RAC forms, and public relations material.
File Plan
Former Classification: I 793.
- Discontinued Rockefeller Archive Center forms, 1976-1994 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Nine Windows by Chagall (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Press Clippings, 1973-1979 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Rockefeller Archive Center - Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Rockefeller Archive Center: A New Facility for Scholars - pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Rockefeller Archive Center, 1974-1980 - pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 6)
- With Compliments of the Rockefeller Archive Center - stationery (Box 1, Folder 7)
- The Rockefeller Archive Center - poster, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- RAC-Related Clippings, 1989-1994 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- The Nelson A. Rockefeller papers at the Rockefeller Archive Center - pamphlet, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- A Chronological History of the Rockefeller Archive Center, 1974-1994 (Box 1, Folder 11)